For with God, Nothing shall be impossible - Luke 1:37
But you, O Load, are a shield around me; you are my glory, the one who holds my head high. - Psalms 3:3
Don't sin by letting anger control you. Think about it overnight and remain silent. - Psalms 4:4
Lead me in the right path,O Lord, or my enemies will conquer me. Make your way plain for me to follow - Psalms 5:8
God is our refuge and strength,always ready to help in times of trouble - Psalms 46:1
Joseph is a fruitful vine, a fruitful vine near a spring, whose branches climb over a wall - Genesis 49:22
Seek Discomfort
Every lie we tell incurs a debt to the truth. Sooner or later that debt is paid - Valery Legasov
Being aware of a single shortcoming within yourself is far more useful than being aware of a thousand in someone else - Dalai Lama
It's alright! - Soul
Live every moment of your life!
"How are you going to spend your life?"...."I'm not sure, but I do know I'm going to live every minute of it."
A delay is better than a disaster
A bit of madness is key